// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "HTML stands for?",
    answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Mark Language",
      "High Text Machine Language",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "HTML comments are represented with",
    answer: "<!--___-->",
    options: [
      "//___",
      "<!--___-->",
      "#___",
      "/*___*/"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who invented HTML?",
    answer: "Tim Berners-Lee",
    options: [
      "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      "Dennis M. Ritchie",
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which Year,HTML discovered",
    answer: "1999",
    options: [
      "2000",
      "1999",
      "2001",
      "1998"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "which version of HTML is currently used?",
    answer: "HTML5",
    options: [
      "HTML2",
      "HTML6",
      "HTML5",
      "HTML7"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "How many types of tags are present in HTML",
     answer: "2 types",
    options: [
       "2 types",
       "1 type",
       "3 types",
       "4 types"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "What is the difference between an opening tag and a closing tag?",
     answer: "",
    options: [
       "Opening tag has a / in front.",
       "Closing tag has a / in front.",
       "There is no difference.",
       "Closing tag has a / back."
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "< br/> What type of tag is this?",
     answer: "break tag",
    options: [
       "break tag",
       "A broken one",
       "An opening tag",
       "none of the above"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Where do all items for the same website need to be saved?",
     answer: "In the same folder",
    options: [
       "In the same folder",
       "A broken one",
       "An opening tag",
       "none of the above"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "How many number of heading tags are present?",
     answer: "6",
    options: [
       "2",
       "3",
       "5",
       "6"
     ]
   }
];
